Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 3: Boxes 45-48
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 3: Boxes 45-48
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 43: Apprentice Training, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 44: Apprentice Training, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 45: Studebaker Dealers in War Production Worl, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 46: Step-by-Step Training of Women, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 47: Employee's handbook, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 48: Agreements Between the Studebaker Corporation and Local 5, UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 49: Agreement Between the Studebaker Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implemnt Workers of America, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 50: Agreement Between the Studebaker Corporation and the International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 51: How to Stay Safely at Studebaker-Packard, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 52: Group Hospitalization Program for retires Employees of Studebaker-Packard Corporation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 53: Studebaker Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 54: Supplemental Agreements Between Studebaker Packard Corporation and the UAW-AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 55: Agreement Between Studebaker-Packard Corporation and the UAW-AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 56: How we Work at Studebaker, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 57: Studebaker Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 58: So Help Me!, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 59: Visibility Zero?, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 60: Rules of Conduct in Studebaker Plant, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 61: What is a Credit Union?, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)